module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which designer has lived in Alaska?', 
    a: 'Haley',
    b: 'Sean',
    c: 'Nick',
    d: 'Darice',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer compared the responsibility of buying a coat to buying a house?', 
    a: 'Chelsb',
    b: 'Mitch',
    c: 'Carolyn',
    d: 'Becky',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer is a closet rock climbing pro?', 
    a: 'Autumn',
    b: 'Sean',
    c: 'West',
    d: 'Nick',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer is a member of a royal bloodline?', 
    a: 'Haley',
    b: 'John',
    c: 'Couv',
    d: 'Libby',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Darice has two shiba inus! What are their names?', 
    a: 'Salt and Pepper',
    b: 'Bubba and Hoss',
    c: 'Shadow and Luna',
    d: 'Whiskers and Potato',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer has a habit of ~stealing~ rescuing plants, and growing them at home?', 
    a: 'Darice',
    b: 'Jessica',
    c: 'West',
    d: 'Becky',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer used to be a science teacher?', 
    a: 'John',
    b: 'Libby',
    c: 'Mitch',
    d: 'Couv',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer orders iced coffee, minus the coffee, when they go to Jos?', 
    a: 'Haley',
    b: 'Libby',
    c: 'Sean',
    d: 'Jessica',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which designer hates mashed potatoes?', 
    a: 'Autumn',
    b: 'Carolyn',
    c: 'Chelsb',
    d: 'Mitch',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a group designers known as collectively?', 
    a: 'A squad',
    b: 'A team',
    c: 'A flock',
    d: 'A cult',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];